First They Killed My Father is a war, drama,
history film directed by Angelina Jolie.
A 5-year-old girl embarks on a harrowing quest for survival amid the sudden
rise and terrifying reign of the Khmer Rouge in Cambodia.
Loung, played by Sareum Srey Moch.
Pa, played by Phoeung Kompheak.
Ma, played by Sveng Socheata.
Kim, played by Mun Kimhak.
Meng, played by Heng Dara.
Khouy, played by Khoun Sothea.
First They Killed My Father (Khmer: មុនដំបូងខ្មែរក្រហមសម្លាប់ប៉ារបស់ខ្ញុំ,
romanized: Mŭn Dâmbong Khmêr Krâhâm Sâmloăb Pa Rôbás Khnhŭm, lit.
'First The Khmer Rouge Killed My Father') is a 2017 Khmer-language biographical
thriller film directed by Angelina Jolie and written by Jolie and Loung Ung.
The film is based on Ung's eponymous memoir.
Set in 1975, the film depicts 5-year-old Loung, who is forced to train as a child soldier
while her siblings are sent to labor camps during the Khmer Rouge regime.
The film was screened at the Telluride Film Festival and 2017 Toronto International Film Festival, and
was released worldwide on Netflix on September 15, 2017, to positive critical reception.
The film explores themes of cambodia, mass murder, 1970s, biography, genocide.
The tone is emotional.